https://dyslexiaaction.org.uk/privacy-policy/

Short CPD Courses for all Education Professionals
Level 5 Specialist SpLD Teaching/Practitioner Qualifications
Level 7 Specialist SpLD Teaching/Practitioner/Assessor Qualifications
Primary and Secondary SpLD Practitioner/Teaching Qualifications
Adult and FE/HE SpLD Qualifications
Courses for International Education Professionals
View our complete range of courses and qualifications
For educators
Assessment Practising Certificate (APC)
Privacy policy
Dyslexia Action is committed to protecting and respecting your privacy.
This policy (together with our terms of use terms and conditions  and any other documents referred to on it) sets out the basis on which any personal data we collect from you, or that you provide to us, will be processed by us.  Please read the following carefully to understand our views and practices regarding your personal data and how we will treat it. We keep certain basic information when you visit our website and recognise the importance of keeping that information secure and letting you know what we will do with it.
For the purpose of the Data Protection Act 1998 (the Act), the data controller is Dyslexia Institute Limited of 10 High Street, Egham, Surrey, TW20 9EA (registration number 1179975).
This policy only applies to our site. If you leave our site via a link or otherwise, you will be subject to the policy of that website provider. We have no control over that policy or the terms of the website and you should check their policy before continuing to access the site.
Information we may collect from you
We may collect and process the following data about you:
Information that you provide by filling in forms on our site. This includes information provided at the time of registering to use our site, subscribing to our service or requesting further services. We may also ask you for information when you report a problem with our site.
If you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence.
We may also ask you to complete surveys that we use for research purposes, although you do not have to respond to them.
Details of your visits to our site including, but not limited to, traffic data, location data, weblogs, operating system, browser usage and other communication data, whether this is required for our own billing purposes or otherwise and the resources that you access.
Where we store your personal data
The data that we collect from you may be transferred to, and stored at, a destination outside the European Economic Area (“EEA”). It may also be processed by staff operating outside the EEA who work for us or for one of our suppliers. Such staff maybe engaged in, among other things, the fulfilment of your order, the processing of your payment details and the provision of support services. By submitting your personal data, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this privacy policy.
All information you provide to us is stored on our secure servers. Any payment transactions will be encrypted. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password which enables you to access certain parts of our site, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share a password with anyone.
Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our site; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access.
Uses made of the information
We use information held about you in the following ways:
To ensure that content from our site is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer.
To provide you with information, products or services that you request from us or which we feel may interest you, where you have consented to be contacted for such purposes.
To carry out our obligations arising from any contracts entered into between you and us.
To allow you to participate in interactive features of our service, when you choose to do so.To notify you about changes to our service.
We may also use your data, or permit selected third parties to use your data, to provide you with information about goods and services which may be of interest to you and we or they may contact you about these by post or telephone.
If you do not want us to use your data in this way, or to pass your details on to third parties for marketing purposes, please tick the relevant box situated on the form on which we collect your data.
Disclosure of your information
We may disclose your personal information to third parties:
In the event that we sell or buy any business or assets, in which case we may disclose your personal data to the prospective seller or buyer of such business or assets.
If we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation, our customers, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organisations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.
Your rights
You have the right to ask us not to process your personal data for marketing purposes. We will usually inform you (before collecting your data) if we intend to use your data for such purposes or if we intend to disclose your information to any third party for such purposes. You can exercise your right to prevent such processing by checking certain boxes on the forms we use to collect your data.  You can also exercise the right at any time by contacting us at trainingcourses@dyslexiaaction.org.uk.
Our site may, from time to time, contain links to and from the websites of our partner networks, advertisers and affiliates.  If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies.  Please check these policies before you submit any personal data to these websites.
Access to information
The Act gives you the right to access information held about you. Your right of access can be exercised in accordance with the Act. Any access request may be subject to a fee of £10 to meet our costs in providing you with details of the information we hold about you.
Changes to our privacy policy
Any changes we may make to our privacy policy in the future will be posted on this page and, where appropriate, notified to you by e-mail. However, we advise that you check this page regularly to keep up to date with any necessary changes.
Contact
Questions, comments and requests regarding this privacy policy are welcomed and should be addressed to trainingcourses@dyslexiaaction.org.uk
Award in Developing Literacy Skills in Learners with Dyslexia – (DAAWD52)
Award in Focal Points for Literacy (DAAWD80)
Award in Learning Support for Adults with Dyslexia – (DAAWD60)
Award in Perspectives on Dyslexia (DAAWD51)
Award in Supporting Adults with Dyslexia and Co-occurring Difficulties – (DAAWD59)
Award in Supporting International Learners with Dyslexia – (DAAWD67)
Certificate in Supporting Adults with Dyslexia and Co-occurring Difficulties (DACRT56)
Certificate in Supporting International Learners with Dyslexia (DACRT67)
Certificate in Supporting Literacy in Learners with Dyslexia (DACRT51) Primary/Secondary
Complete range of Courses and Qualifications
CPD Short Courses for teaching professionals at all levels
CPD Courses: Dyslexia, Literacy and Numeracy
CPD Short Courses: Beyond Dyslexia and Literacy
Dyslexia Action Literacy Programme (DALP) Award for Practitioners (DAAWD85)
Level 5 (Undergraduate) SpLD Teacher/Practitioner Qualifications
Level 7 Professional Certificate in Structured Teaching Intervention for Dyslexia and Literacy
Training to become a Specialist SpLD Assessor
Training to become a Specialist SpLD Teacher/Practitioner
About Us
Why study with us?
Dyslexia Action is a trading name of Real Group Ltd, Company No 06556128, VAT Reg No 837306132
Log into Moodle
